Hello, my name is Pyo Ye-Rim...
By the time you see this video,
I will be about to end my life...
unless I already have.
She had spoken out on social media
about the bullying she suffered
at school when she was young..
The police are investigating
the e circumstances of her death.
She announced her intention
to end her life in a video online.
She said that she was really struggling
with the criticism aimed at her
after she had spoken out against bullying.
Pyo Ye Rim died by suicide on October 10,
2023.
She was 27 years old.
She had become a whistleblower,
an activist speaking out against violence in schools.
Violins,
which she herself endured for 12 years.
She grew up in this coastal region in the southeast of the country.
where she was bullied year after year,
all the way up to the end of secondary school.
What she went through could happen to anyone.
Anyone could have been traumatised like
she was, and suffered the consequences.
My name is Kim Hyo-Kyung.
I'm 28 years old.
I spent a year at the same girls' school as Ye-Rim.
As soon as she went to class,
the other pupils bullied her.
They hit her.
They would storm into the classroom, shouting
and insulting her. They kicked her desk.
They dragged her to the toilet
and plunged her head into the bowl.
I can only imagine how badly
she wanted to get away.
Pyongye Rim was the first to go public with her story.
We met her a few weeks before her death to bring attention to her cause.
Her contribution was central to our film on bullying in South Korea.
I have often wondered whether
I should go on living through all this.
Whether I have to die for it to stop.
One day, at secondary school or high school, I don't
know which, a girl came in the middle of class.
She came in and told me to follow her.
I left without suspecting anything.
She beat me up for 10 minutes, without mercy.
And all this while the teacher was in class.
He told me I was the one who wasn't
making an effort to get on with the others.
He said, 'Are you sure you
haven't done anything to them?"
She didn’t go to college after the second degree of school
She was to affraid of running to the people who had bullied her
She opened a hairdressing salon and tried to rebuild her life.
We started filming with her here at the salon.
At the time,
no one suspected what she was going through,
not even her parents.
Ten years later,
she decided to tell her story to the whole country.
Thousands of young Koreans identified with her.
An 11-year-old primary school pupil
died by suicide yesterday morning.
A primary school pupil took his own life
"because of bullying at school".
Korea has the highest suicide rate in the world.
There are more than 30 recorded cases every day.
And suicides often lead the news.
The rate is especially high among young people and among those who are bullied at school.
With
60,000 cases reported each year,
films,
books and TV series all show this national crisis in their storylines.
One of the latest hit series tells the story of a model pupil who ends up standing up to his attackers.
This is exactly what Pyo Ye Rim dared to do.
When she spoke out on social media about what had happened to her,
she received some support,
but also thousands of attacks.
It was a wave of cyberbullying.
She had not anticipated the...
violence and scale of it the issue of school violence long a taboo subject
has inflamed public opinion journalist Lee Ye Wong was the last person to speak with Pyo Ye Rim
she believes that Pyo Ye Rim made it possible for other people to speak out
You could say that she died
for her cause, like a martyr.
Not many victims of bullying reveal
their identity to the general public,
so I think that's why she had such an influence.
In recent years, more and more voices
have spoken out to say that this had to stop,
that the scourge of school violence had to end.
Pyo Ye-Rim embodied this turning point
in society by denouncing the system.
Whenever she had free time,
she studied the laws on bullying at school.
She was very committed to her fight.
She set up an organization to help other victims.
A few months before her death,
she launched a petition to hold bullies to account for their actions.
This lawyer,
John Ho Sung,
helped her to collect more than 50,000 signatures.
Together they worked on a bill to revise the statute of limitations in cases of violence in schools.
Pyo Ye Rim was never able to bring her bullies to justice.
They are now adults and the statute of limitations has expired.
This is precisely the change that she wanted to make.
They worked with this MP on their proposal which is due to be submitted to parliament.
She was surprised by the
number of signatures collected.
I tried very hard to comfort Pyo.
I told her that you would be
the one who could help us.
I explained that with your support, you would
get this law passed as quickly as possible.
Obviously, I still have to work to ensure
that the bill has every chance of being passed.
The petition you've launched will
be a great help, that's for sure.
And will enable us to go
even further in our requests.
We need to change our penal code and the law.
Victims, even years after the event,
must be able to lodge a complaint.
They must be able to defend
themselves and obtain compensation.
This is the only way to protect our young people.
Minors must be able to take action
once they have become adults.
I know a lot of people who have been
through what Pyo Ye-Rim went through.
But she is one of the rare people
to have spoken out publicly on this issue.
Today, bullying at school is
a real issue in Korean society.
Any high-ranking official, celebrity
or public figure who is involved, or even sees
his or her children directly or indirectly involved
in a case of bullying, has questions to answer...
This subject is getting a lot of attention today.
But at the time when Pyo Ye-Rim was going
through all this, it wasn't yet the case.
It's an important issue,
so much so that a hashtag was created in 2023.
Call out your bully.
It was like Me Too,
but for violence in school.
Tens of thousands of stories flooded social media platforms.
People denounced their bullies publicly years later.
There was such an unprecedented wave of accusations that it sometimes started to look like a witch hunt.
Not even celebrities have been spared.
Singers,
sportsmen and women,
actors,
actresses,
senior civil servants.
Anyone involved in bullying in any way could be ostracized,
lose their job or be forced to resign.
There is a lot of talk,
but no action to address the problem.
Two hours from Seoul,
there is a unique school.
It's a boarding school for children and teenagers who have been victims of bullying and have developed school phobia.
Even if their bullies have been reported,
they're too scared of reprisals once they are back in class.
Today we're welcoming a new pupil.
He's a very nice boy.
I'm relying on you to make him feel welcome.
In this boarding school,
around 50 teenagers receive a traditional education alongside counselling.
Is the water here the sea or...?
The children live here in a safe space and stay as long as it takes before they can go back to school.
It might be a few weeks or even several months.
16-year-old Min Sam Mool arrived a week ago.
I had nowhere to go, I was completely lost.
But I couldn't give up my
studies either, so I came here.
If you ask any of us to go back
to school, none of us want to go.
We're all the same, even those with more money.
It's our last option because we've reached our limit.
The centre,
which has seven other regional branches,
is entirely private.
privately funded.
There are no other facilities of this type in Korea apart from psychiatric hospitals.
For many parents,
like Min Sam-mool's parents,
this is a last resort.
I had a lot of questions...
I wanted to listen to someone who had
been through the same experience
to find out how to help my child feel better.
That's the kind of help I came here for.
Before, we were completely lost,
even when we were at home.
It was affecting my work.
For us, this centre not only cares for
young people, but also for us parents.
I saw my child's confidence
plummet when he was bullied.
Right up to the point where he
talked about taking his own life.
Obviously, as parents, we have a
lot of expectations of our children.
I always wanted mine to do better than me.
That's why I asked a lot of him,
demanding that he get over this quickly.
But he never really regained his self-confidence.
During that time, he actually
attempted suicide, which I witnessed.
Since then, I've radically changed my opinion.
It doesn't matter whether he studies well or not,
all that matters is that he's alive beside me...
And that he has a long life.
These parents are often at a loss.
They're powerless in the face of their children's bullies,
who can even sue for defamation.
This actually happened to me.
When we accused the culprits,
they accused us of defamation.
And how did that make you feel?
Well, I was taking a walk when I saw
a letter from lawyers, and I fainted twice.
My head was spinning, and my legs
couldn't carry me. I really did fall twice.
And I couldn't sleep at night. It was so difficult.
The hardest thing is accepting
that a lawyer has decided
to help guilty people get away with what they did.
All they did was lie and accuse my daughter of
being responsible for the cruelty she suffered.
We are the ones who have suffered because of them.
Not only did they refuse to apologise,
but they also attacked us.
For us, it was like rubbing salt in the wound.
Rather than acknowledge the facts,
the bullies counterattack.
Bullies will sue for defamation to avoid the serious consequences of being held accountable.
In 2026,
a national database will be set up,
and all those found guilty of bullying will be banned from the best universities.
So they deny it and call the victims liars,
insult them and threaten them.
There are two ways of overcoming fear.
Either you try to put it aside...
or you give way to anger..
I'm angry.
And that anger will make me a strong woman.
Don't try and stop me.
Don't think I'm making this video
to get back at you or to scare anyone.
I'm making it for the students
who are being bullied right now,
and against those who are committing
crimes at this very moment.
Lee Se-wook was the first to share Pyongye Rim's story online.
He's what's known in Korea as a netizen,
an internet vigilante,
and whistleblower.
I was the one who contacted the national channels
Her story made the headlines
and changed public opinion.
Immediately, a girl who probably
went to the same school
as Pyo Ye-Rim showed all the faces
and names of the alleged culprits.
Everything moved very fast on social media.
People became interested in her attackers.
Some of them lost their jobs or had to resign
in the face of the avalanche of criticism.
Pyo Ye-Rim was pleased.
She said that she was lucky to have won
people's hearts, which had made it possible
to finally pinpoint the culprits.
But she didn't want to stop there.
Education in Korea is very much
marked by the legacy
here again,
Education in Korea is very much
marked by the legacy
of the Japanese occupation that we experienced.
It's a military system where the interests of
the group take precedence over the individual.
If a single person endangers the group, even
slightly, they end up being completely rejected.
I think it's a culture that's
very deeply rooted in our society.
It permeates the Korean education
system and has never disappeared.
When a student is abused or left out,
they are rejected to protect the majority.
Pyo Ye-rim underestimated the outpouring of hatred on social media that would follow her revelations.
Her bullies resurfaced.
It must have surprised them.
They had forgotten everything.
The bullies must have thought,
"Why is she bringing this up again?"
They ended up killing Ye-Rim.
Just as much as she killed herself.
Many more people drove her
to suicide than you might think.
When she told her story of bullying,
many people sided with the guilty.
Some criticised her for only
speaking out now and said
that she hadn't really suffered
12 years of harassment.
Her bullies were not the only
ones responsible for her death.
A very large number of people are.
The school system is another factor,
as it often pushes pupils to their limit.
Every evening in the capital,
Seoul,
busloads of students are taken to the hagyons,
private after-school academies where they will do another full day of classes.
That's what it takes to pass the university entrance exam.
Many of them study for up to 20 hours a day.
It's a highly competitive environment,
and parents share this obsession with success.
This academy pushes you
to study harder than any other.
If you study for fifteen hours a day, for example,
you have three hours to eat and six hours to sleep.
All they do is study, sleep and eat.
Parents spend little time with their children,
and they expect teachers to focus on imparting as much knowledge as possible.
This parallel system of private schools has become the norm in Korea.
The government has even tried to regulate them by imposing a
10pm closing time.
I think it's hard to change the
system because, at the end of the day,
competition is the mainstay of private education.
At the end of the day, if you want to get into the
university of your dreams and get the job you want,
you have to accept this competitive system.
But with all of this pressure on achievement,
no one seems to be focusing on the students'
problems with socialization.
The pressure might be one of the factors behind violence in schools.
Pyongyang Rim revealed the hidden face of the school system.
Education had a positive image in Korea based on the entire nation's academic success.
It was held up as being the gold standard.
But vulnerable pupils were left to cope without support.
Other citizens now want to challenge this system.
Like Kim Jong-ki,
he knew Pyongyang Rim well and knew about her campaign and her commitment.
They were supposed to work together,
but that was before she took her own life.
He didn't see it coming,
just as he didn't see it coming when his own
13-year-old lost his life to suicide.
I felt a pain that no other parent
should feel in their life.
It was like the sky fell on me,
and everything descended into chaos.
I find it very difficult to express
my pain in front of others.
I prefer to stay alone to think, talk and pray.
I see myself as a bad father who didn't
pay attention to his son's suffering.
I was too focused on my work
to help with his problems.
I feel very ashamed.
I've lost all will to live.
Why live when I couldn't protect him?
What's the point of being a company boss
and making millions?
His son Kim Dae-hyun died by suicide after jumping out of the window of the family's fifth floor flat.
He had never mentioned his suffering from being regularly bullied.
He never looked happy.
For a while before he died, he would come back
with wounds, bruises, broken glasses.
It happened almost every day.
I met his attackers in a bakery.
I asked each of them why they had hurt my son.
They were trembling with fear.
They stuttered and kept apologising.
Their attitude destroyed me.
I wanted to kill them. Well, not with
my own hands, I couldn't do that.
I planned to hire an organisation
to kill them in Korea,
before leaving the country to settle
in South America or Africa.
That was my plan.
I was ready to do it, but when I saw them
trembling in front of me, I felt sorry for them.
I don't know if you can understand.
This tragedy shook Kim Jong-ki very deeply.
He was wracked with guilt for not having been able to protect his son.
So he set up his own foundation to help victims and their parents.
He regularly appeals to the public.
public authorities.
And he feels that they still don't fully appreciate the scale of the problem.
The consequences are devastating.
Hundreds more families suffer bereavement every year.
Kim Jong-ki's foundation now has 14 branches.
throughout South Korea,
with 300 employees and as many volunteers.
It has set up counselling and psychological support units with telephone help lines for parents and pupils.
And what did you try to do?
The school said they were going to separate them,
but my child has only been able to go
to school one day in the last nine months.
Hello.
I'm Kim Jong-ki, it's good to meet you.
Today,
he is meeting a father of two children,
whose 13-year-old daughter has just taken her own life.
My poor man, I'm sorry for your loss.
When I hear the sound of the wind,
I think of how my daughter
must have felt when she jumped
from the 15th floor of our building.
That is so sad.
I have a lot of regrets.
If I could have done something
when she was still alive,
I wouldn't be so desperate and apathetic.
After she died, I was angry,
but now I don't even have that strength.
I'm afraid to go any further.
All I have left is my son...
Isn't your first priority to take care of your family?
Yes, it is.
You must stand strong for them.
That's your role as a father.
You are the backbone of your home.
Every day,
this father stands in front of the school,
distraught.
He's trying to understand what happened to his daughter,
but he's all alone.
He's left calling out to the pupils,
trying to get from them the answers that the school won't give him.
My daughter is dead! My daughter is dead!
She sent you a message before she died!
You were the last person she spoke to!
Tell me what happened!
She jumped from the 15th floor!
We take on a huge number of similar cases.
These wounds are almost impossible to heal.
More than individuals, it's the
whole family that breaks down.
No one can cope alone,
and no one knows how to deal with it.
And neither the school nor the
Ministry of Education will help them.
He had planned some joint interventions at school
along side Pyongyang Rim
The program is called Asago,
the confession.
It aims to get people talking about bullying.
Pupils are called on to anonymously recount their experiences as bullies,
as victims or just as witnesses.
You know, my videos are shown
in a lot of schools, like this one,
where I'm sometimes invited
to talk about school bullying.
I'm "Mr Bullying.
In fact, I had a beautiful son like all of you here,
but I lost him because of bullying at school.
I've decided to quit my job in
favour of this kind of activity,
so that no one goes through the same thing.
Hundreds of confessions are collected every term in this school.
then explored in discussion groups to try and understand each other's feelings and experiences.
I saw him push you and insult you.
I'm sorry I didn't say anything.
I'm really sorry I didn't help you.
I have a friend who has been bullied
since the beginning of the year.
I feel guilty because I can't talk to him about
it for fear of how other people will look at me.
A student might open up if you
talk to them, joke with them,
have a laugh and have a good time together.
Above all, you need to create an atmosphere
conducive to discussion and a relationship of trust.
But that's hard to do, and that's why
most of them don't tell their parents.
Does anyone here spend at least 5 hours
a week with their parents to talk or anything?
That many people?
My mum often asks me how things are at school.
I answer her, but sometimes she
complains that I don't talk enough.
Wouldn't it be nice if you could talk to your parents?
Because if they know you well, they'll be able
to help or support you if you run into a problem.
If you don't say anything, they won't know.
My son never told me the truth either.
So I couldn't have known...
Goodbye! Take care.
When we met Pyo Ye Rim,
we went back to see her old school.
She hadn't been back there since she left school.
It's overwhelming to realise what I've been through.
When you look at that little school it's
hard to imagine how frightening it was.
What kept me from running away and hiding?
I wish I could have escaped.
I regret not having been happy for so many years.
I live with this disappointment.
Now I have to learn to live with
these memories and move on.
I need to be happy in my life.
Pyo Ye Rim was never able to build a new life for herself.
She used social media to fight her battle.
But she received an outpouring of hateful messages on those same platforms.
A never-ending cycle.
We had planned one final shoot to finish the film.
Mum, dad, I'm sorry, for everything until I die.
It's all my fault.
You told me that life had no meaning without me,
but I'm not going to be able to listen to you.
I can't begin to imagine your pain...
the pain of seeing your child go first. I'm so sorry.
I'm ashamed to admit it, even though I'm giving up,
but I dare to hope that other
people won't give up my fight.
My death may not mean much, but I beg you,
at least let my petition be useful and let this
law be seriously considered until it is applied.
I rely on you.
One year after her death,
There is no change in the situation.
The bill has still not been passed.
Acts of bullying at school are still subject to a three-year statute of limitations.